heymarket.com 2019-09-18

# Privacy Policy - Heymarket

Effective Date: _November 18, 2015_

## Our Policy

Welcome to the application (collectively, the “App”) of Common Sun, Inc. (“Common Sun”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This App is operated by Common Sun and has been created to provide information about our company and its telephony services (the “Services”) to our users (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth Common Sun’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from App visitors and users of the Services.

## Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the App or the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

### Personal Data That You Provide Through the App:

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information such as when you register for access to the Services, use certain Services, contact us with inquiries or respond to one of our surveys. Wherever Common Sun collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Common Sun and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.

Non-Identifiable or Aggregated Data: When you interact with Common Sun through the App or Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Common Sun may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Common Sun affiliates, agents or service providers. This App may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our App, the number of visitors to each page of our App, the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers and how our users use and interact with the Common Sun Service. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Common Sun often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. Common Sun may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. Common Sun may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

In operating this App, we may also use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our App gives to your browser when you access the App. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the App and help us analyze App usage more accurately. For instance, our App may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the App without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the App. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off.

### Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

Common Sun uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Common Sun and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the App to help us improve the content and functionality of the App, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. Common Sun and its Related Companies may use this information to communicate with you regarding the Services or to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. Note however that as user of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If Common Sun intends to use any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below: 911 Calls and Requests for Emergency Assistance. NOTE THAT THE SERVICE CAN NOT AND SHOULD NOT BE USED FOR 911 OR EMERGENCY CALLING.

### Business Transfers:

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data that we have retained about you may be part of the transferred assets.

We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:

Common Sun, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

### Legal Requirements:

Common Sun may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation or valid legal process, or (ii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the App or the public.

## Your Choices

You can use the App without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Services.

### Our Deletion of Your Personal Data and other information:

You may request that your account be deleted by contacting [help@heymarket.com](mailto:help@heymarket.com). Upon deleting your account, we remove the phone number and it may be re-assigned. Backup copies of this data are not immediately deleted, however, and some aspects of user history are maintained for longer periods of time so that we can reconcile our records and manage our business. Please be advised that we have no control over data that may be captured by third parties through your use of the Services, including but not limited to your carrier, internet service provider, Apple, and third-party vendors we may rely on to perform the services, except that we will not disclose Personal Data to third parties other than as permitted in this Privacy Policy.

## Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Common Sun other than Personal Data collected through the App or Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Common Sun through this App or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the App, such as public profiles (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Common Sun shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

### Children:

Common Sun’ Terms of Service prohibit use of the App by children under the age of 18, and Common Sun and does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use or submit any Personal Data through the App. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 18 has provided Personal Data to Common Sun through this App, please contact us.

### Links to Other Web Apps:

This Privacy Policy applies only to the App. This App may contain links to other web Apps not operated or controlled by Common Sun (the “Third Party Apps”). The policies and procedures we describe here do not apply to the Third Party Apps. The links from this App do not imply that Common Sun endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Apps. We suggest contacting those Apps directly for information on their privacy policies.

### Integrating Third Party Services within the Services:

Some features of the Service allows you to enable various online third party services, such as social media and networking services (“Third Party Services”), to be directly integrated into your Common Sun experience. By directly integrating these services, we make your online experiences richer, and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature, we may ask you to provide us login authorization for the relevant Third Party Services. By enabling such Third Party Services, you are allowing us to pass your information to these service providers for this purpose. When you add a Third Party Service account to the Service, we will collect your login information and other relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service. However, please remember that the manner in which Third Party Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and Common Sun shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third Party Service that may be enabled within the Service.

### Users From Outside the United States:

The Services are hosted in the United States and user of the Services is governed by United States law. If you are using the Services from outside the United States, please be aware that your Data may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Services, you consent to your Data being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Security

Common Sun takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the App from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us or transmit via the services.

## Other Terms and Conditions:

Your access to and use of this App is subject to the Terms of Service.

## Changes to Common Sun’s Privacy Policy:

The App, services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Common Sun to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Common Sun reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the App after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update, correct, or delete Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via this App or the Services.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Common Sun’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of this App. You may contact us as via email at [legal@heymarket.com](mailto:legal@heymarket.com), or via postal mail at Common Sun, Attn: Privacy, 2443 Fillmore St #510, San Francisco, CA 94115.
